<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chashabad</string>
    <string name="guide_text">For Information Tap on Image</string>
    <string name="lang_btn_text">বাংলা</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seed">Onion seed</string>
    <string name="seed_text">
        "Onions are considered a cool-season vegetable."
        "But they can be planted at two different times of the year, depending upon growing zone."
        "After planting seeds, keep the soil moist at all times."
        "Seeds capable of germinating contain both an embryo and food reserves within their protective seed coat."
        "Soil moisture softens the seed coat and enters the seed through a process call imbibition."
        "Once inside the seed, the moisture triggers cellular respiration and metabolization of the food reserves."
        "seeds germinate in about ten days."

    </string>
    <string name="seedling_text">
    	"The first stage of germination is radicle emergence."
        "The radicle anchors the seed in place and supports the growing seedling."
        "The radicle collects moisture and nutrients to sustain plant growth."
        "The sprout emerges through the weakened seed covering, eventually breaking the soil’s surface."
        "Soon after, the first real leaves appear, resembling a smaller and fleshier version of the plant’s mature leaves, signifying a shift in the plant’s development as the seedling begins to obtain energy through photosynthesis."

    </string>
    <string name="vine_text">
       "At this stage, the small onion plant begins to build its root system."
        "The seedling produces more roots and a few more adult leaves before initiating rapid vegetative growth."

        "The leaves of an onion develop swiftly during vegetative growth."
        "Onions starts with just a few leaves, grow eight to ten healthy leaves in weeks."
        "The leaf development stops when the onion is ready to produce the bulb."
    </string>
    <string name="flower_text">
        "When developing onions have at least four leaves, they are ready to put their energy toward bulb production."
        "The existing leaves continue to grow and elongate, increasing the available surface area for photosynthesis."
        "Each leaf represents a scale that eventually becomes one of the bulb’s rings."
        "The leaf sheaths swell to form the central storage tissue of the bulbs."
        "After a few weeks, the onion’s bulb emerges from the ground, revealing the onion’s top."
        "Onions are ready for harvest when the tops become droopy and turn brown."

    </string>
    <string name="fruit_text">
       "After 70 – 90 days, onions are fully mature and ready to harvest."
        "Onions reach optimal growth right before they reach maturity — when the bulbs are just starting to develop and the tops are the width of a pencil."
        "Onions can still be picked after that, but mature green onions have a spicier flavor."

    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_text">
       "If onions are not harvested and left in the ground during the winter, they will regrow in the spring."
        "The underground bulbs are already fibrous and woody at this point."
        "Because the root system was established the previous year, the plant can focus its entire energy on sending up new shoots to emerge through the soil surface. "
        "The air and soil temperatures rise as the weather warms, and the plant begins to bolt."
        "Bolting refers to the crop suddenly growing a flowering stalk."
        "When this happens, the plant abruptly stops vegetative growth and prepares for the end of its life cycle."
        "Buds appear once the stalk has fully matured and the top of the plant blooms with a white or purple flower."
        "Birds, bees, and butterflies pollinate the colorful, round flower heads containing seeds. After the seeds appear, the onion plant’s life cycle is complete."

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seedling">Germination</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vine">Vegetative</string>
    <string name="title_activity_flower">Bulb Formation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fruit">Maturation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cucumber">Reproduction</string>
    <string name="title_text">Life Cycle of Onion</string>
</resources>